So far, we've looked at both the foundational redundancy pieces that AWS
到目前为止我们都看到了 AWS 的两个基本冗余
has and regions and Availability Zones as well as resilience within application services.
区域和可用性区域以及应用程序服务中的弹性
Now we'll take a look at
现在我们看看
understanding business objectives and how this relates to our work here.
了解业务目标以及这与我们这里工作的关系
Later, we'll discuss reacting to failure.
稍后 我们将讨论对失败的反应
In this lesson, we'll start by discussing uptime.
在本课程中 我们将开始讨论正常运行时间
What it is and how to measure it.
它是什么 如何衡量
The opposite of uptime is downtime.
与正常运行时间相反的是停机时间
Downtime isn't quite as straightforward as it appears.
停机时间不像看上去那么简单
We'll learn different types of downtime and how to account for them.
我们将了解不同类型的停机时间以及如何对其进行计算
RTO is the Recovery Time Objective.
RTO 是恢复时间目标
This is your commitment,
这是你的承诺
the maximum amount of time that your service would be down.
您的服务将停机的最长时间
Recovery Point Objective or
恢复点目标或
RP0 is the maximum amount of time over which you would lose data.
RP0 是丢失数据的最大时间量
These are commitments that you would make
这些是你做出的承诺
internally but also contractually to your customers.
在内部 也在合同上给您的客户
Disaster recovery is the extreme of availability and resiliency.
灾难恢复是可用性和弹性的极端
It refers to bringing up your systems in another place,
它是指在另一个地方建立你的系统
typically another AWS region.
通常是另一个 AWS 区域
This would only be done in the case of a complete region outage or other disaster.
只有在完全地区中断或其他灾难的情况下才会这样做